Shirin Labbai shirlabbai@gmail.com Pune, Maharashtra.

Mobile:7498819100

Career Objective:

To be associated with a dynamic team in a progressive organization that gives me the scope to apply and enrich my knowledge and skills with continual learning and professional growth.

Experience Summary:

Highly accomplished professional supplemented on IT Infrastructure & systems, having over 3.8 years of rich and insightful experience as Sr. System Administrator.

Organization: Fiserv

Designation :Senior Associate System Administrator

Client :Banking Clients
Role :System Admin

Duration :Sep 2019- Aug 2022

Responsibilities & Skills:

- Provided support to US banks as their IT support Using SolarWinds N Central Tool
- Monitoring System Performances through infrastructure alerts and Malfunction.
 (Alerts: Connectivity Failed, Disk Utilization, CPU utilization, Memory Utilization, Services, etc)
- Supported various Desktop, Laptops and Printers models available in their environment
- Support windows related issues escalated by Remote Support
- Manage ServiceNow incident and request workflows by taking ownership, prioritizing incoming work, and delivering services meeting defined Service Level Agreement (SLA) timelines
- Resolve and respond to user questions received via ServiceNow, email or other collaboration methods meeting defined in SLA
- Used technical knowledge bases (internal & external) to resolve technical issues & collaborate on issues with relevant teams as required
- Windows Desktop troubleshooting
- Managing backups using software like Veritas Backup
- Managing security through Crowdstrike
- Windows server and Workstation Patching on Monthly basis through N central
- Linux server Patching
- Creating Monthly and Quarterly reports for Clients
- Vulnerability Management for multiple banking clients
- Active Directory: User, groups, creation, and assignment of rights

Organization: Innovation Technology by Design

Designation :System Administrator **Client** :Rose Computers MSP

Role :Sr.Associate System Administrator

Duration :Aug 2022 – Till Date

Responsibilities & Skills:

- Managed helpdesk for Strategic Risk Solutions Insurance company
- Worked with the helpdesk to resolve issues related to 0365, user management and Azure Active Directory
- Threat locker deployment, assigning machines into learning and secure mode Also, uninstalling Threat locker
- Worked on Darkweb Compromises using Kaseya
- Managed internal application "Sage" for SRS users
- Managed "Infor and Query" analysis tool for SRS users
- Working on ConnectWise Automate and Manage, Screen Connect, using ITGlue to obtain credentials in order to login to the machines
- Creating office 365 user accounts and assigning licenses, adding or removing them from groups as per need from exchange admin center
- Creating and Managing Active Directory user accounts and assigning specific roles and permissions to the users as per demand, joining machines to the domain
- Managing Physical and Virtual Microsoft Windows Servers 2008,2012, 2016
- Creating lifecycle reports for clients

Technical Skills

- End user Support: Hardware and Software Support, MS Office & Application Support, Printer Support, Desktop Network Connectivity Support, Third Party Application Support
- Active Directory: User Administration, Access Management, Group/OU Management.
- Server (Windows & Linux) & Workstation Patching, WSUS, N-Central.
- Veritas Backups Monitoring.
- Crowdstrike Security Administration.
- vSphere & Azure: VM Deployment, Snapshots, Resource Management & Monitoring.

Key Skills

- M365 & Azure AD
- Windows Troubleshooting and Patch management
- Server and Workstation Monitoring
- Linux patch management
- Vulnerability management
- Backup Monitoring Veritas
- Azure Portal
- Team Collaboration

Tools

- Ncentral Monitoring Tool
- Service Now Ticketing Tool
- Client 360 Ticketing Tool
- Continuum RMM

- Connectwise Manage Ticketing Tool
- Threatlocker
- IT Glue Documentation
- Dashlane
- Sophos Central
- Darkweb Kesaya

Education

Bachelor of Engineering in Computers MMCOE, Pune | August 2014 - June 2019

• Completed my Computer Engineering from Pune University

Affiliations

- Successfully implemented and upgraded enterprise-level systems. Successfully managed complex IT projects and improved customer satisfaction while maintaining compliance with industry regulations.
- Received appreciation from Team Manager for consistently completing every task with professionalism.

Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi
- Tamil

Personal Information:

• Father's Name : Rijuratdullah M Labbai

Date of Birth : 26rd Dec, 1996.

• Languages known : English, Hindi, Marathi and Tamil.

• Passport Number : S5113569

I confirm that the above Information given by me is true to the best of my knowledge.

Shirin Labbai